This is a situation that happens to me quite often because I like to go to coffee shops to work.
这种情况经常发生在我身上，因为我喜欢去咖啡店工作。
OK so I go to the coffee shop and I'm working on my computer.
好的，所以我去咖啡店，我正在使用我的电脑。
And then I need to go to the bathroom but if I take my computer with me to the bathroom then I might
然后我需要去洗手间，但如果我带着我的电脑去洗手间，那么我可能会
lose my seat.
失去我的座位。
Maybe I have a very good seat.
也许我有一个很好的座位。
Well that's not good.
那不好。
But if I leave my computer.
但是如果我离开我的电脑。
Well then maybe it will be stolen.
那么也许它会被偷走。
It will be stolen.
它会被偷走。
I don't want that to happen.
我不希望这种情况发生。
Actually recently I had a bicycle stolen.
其实最近我有一辆自行车被偷了。
So it's not fun to have your stuff stolen.
所以你的东西被偷了并不好玩。
OK.
好的。
So you look over there and there's a person and they have a computer.
所以你往那边看，有一个人，他们有一台电脑。
So you think they must be pretty reliable reliable and they're probably not going to steal your computer.
因此，您认为它们一定非常可靠可靠，并且它们可能不会窃取您的计算机。
You would like them to watch.
您希望他们观看。
Look at not all the time.
不是一直看。
Not like staring but pay attention to your computer while you go to the bathroom.
不像盯着看，而是在你去洗手间时注意你的电脑。
OK.
好的。
You're going to ask them to do that.
你会要求他们这样做。
This is a common thing to do in America.
这在美国很常见。
Very common.
很常见。
And then you can come back and then you can have your seat back.
然后你可以回来，然后你可以让你的座位回来。
Now it is something that we do that requires trust a little bit because you don't know that person.
现在我们做的事情需要一点信任，因为你不认识那个人。
But they seem fairly reliable.
但它们似乎相当可靠。
It's your judgment it's your judgment that they seem reliable.
这是您的判断，您的判断是它们看起来可靠。
So you're at a coffee shop and you need to go to the bathroom but your computer is on the table.
所以你在咖啡店，你需要去洗手间，但你的电脑在桌子上。
You see a stranger sitting nearby and they seem fairly reliable.
你看到一个陌生人坐在附近，他们看起来相当可靠。
What can you say.
你能说什么。
OK now we're going to use a very common expression to go up to this person.
好的，现在我们将使用一个非常常见的表达方式来接近这个人。
I'm going to put it in the situation so I walk up to that person and I say Excuse me.
我要把它放在这种情况下，所以我走到那个人面前说对不起。
Now I could add here sorry to bother you.
现在我可以在这里添加抱歉打扰您。
Sorry sorry to bother you.
抱歉打扰您了。
Sorry to bother you.
抱歉打扰你。
You could take this out.
你可以把这个拿出来。
You could take this up.
你可以接受这个。
You could say just sorry to bother you.
你可以说对不起打扰你了。
You could say hi there.
你可以在那里打个招呼。
Sorry to bother you.
抱歉打扰你。
There are a lot of different ways that you could begin.
您可以通过多种不同的方式开始。
Excuse me is a very common thing to say in general to a stranger when you want to say something to them.
当您想对陌生人说些什么时，请原谅我是很常见的事情。
Excuse me is a great way to if you need to talk to somebody you don't know to begin that whatever it
如果您需要与不认识的人交谈，请原谅我是一个很好的方式
is you need to say excuse me.
你需要说对不起吗？
Sorry to bother you could you could you.
很抱歉打扰你，你能不能。
Now here's the expression.
现在是表达式。
Keep an eye on my computer while I go to the bathroom and you could add then I'll be back in a minute.
当我去洗手间时，请留意我的电脑，你可以补充一下，然后我会在一分钟内回来。
Back means you'll return.
回来意味着你会回来。
I'll be back in a minute.
我会在一分钟内回来。
I'll be right back or I'll.
我会马上回来，否则我会。
We could say also.
我们也可以说。
I'll I'll just be a minute.
我会的，我会等一会。
I'll just be a minute.
我一会儿就好。
So this is a very common thing to say in this situation.
所以在这种情况下这是很常见的说法。
There are other things you could say but keep an eye on is the is the useful expression here.
您还可以说其他内容，但请注意这里有用的表达方式。
Excuse me sorry to bother you could you keep an eye on my computer.
对不起，打扰您了，请您留意我的电脑。
Well I go to the bathroom.
嗯，我去洗手间。
I'll just be a minute.
我一会儿就好。
Or would you mind.
或者你会介意。
Would you mind keeping if you use would you mind then we can say keeping.
如果您使用，您会介意保留吗？那么我们可以说保留。
But it's the same expression.
但这是相同的表达方式。
Would you mind keeping an eye on my computer while I go to the bathroom.
我去的时候你介意看一下我的电脑吗到浴室。
I'll be back in a minute.
我会在一分钟内回来。
I'll be back in a couple of minutes and they'll probably say yes sure.
我会在几分钟后回来，他们可能会说是的。
Yeah sure sure.
是的，当然。
No problem.
没问题。
All right.
好的。
That's OK.
没关系。
Then when you come back you have to because your computer is over there.
然后，当您回来时，您必须这样做，因为您的计算机在那边。
Don't do nothing.
不要什么都不做。
You'll have to do something it's sort of polite it's unspoken rule when you come back.
你必须做一些礼貌的事情，这是你回来时的潜规则。
You look at them if they're far enough away you don't have to actually shout across the coffee shop
如果它们足够远，您就可以看着它们，而不必在咖啡店里大喊大叫
things like that.
像这样的东西。
You can just say thank you.
你可以说谢谢。
Like that and whisper it to yourself.
像那样对自己耳语。
Wave like that and say then you have acknowledged that they did something for you.
像那样挥手，然后说你已经承认他们为你做了什么。
You don't need to go over to them and say thank you very much for helping me.
你不需要走到他们面前说非常感谢你帮助我。
Here's my business card.
这是我的名片。
It's a little too much because it's a very simple common thing.
这有点太多了，因为这是一件非常简单的普通事情。
This expression.
这个表情。
Keep an eye on can be used in lots of other ways.
密切关注可以用于许多其他方式。
Now if I'm watching the computer does it really mean that that person has one eye on their computer
现在，如果我在看电脑，这真的意味着那个人的一只眼睛在看他们的电脑吗？
and one eye on my computer.
一只眼睛盯着我的电脑。
No.
不。
Doesn't mean that what it means is they're paying attention to it.
并不意味着这意味着他们正在关注它。
They're not looking at it every moment that I'm gone.
他们不会在我离开的每一刻都看着它。
They're just paying attention so we can use it to mean to pay attention to something or to care about
他们只是在关注，所以我们可以用它来表示关注某事或关心
the condition of something.
某事的状况。
So we could use keep an eye on for example for children for a week maybe for example going on vacation.
因此，我们可以使用 keep an eye on 例如一周的孩子，例如去度假。
I have a young child and I ask my my mother do you think you could keep an eye on Joseph for the week.
我有一个年幼的孩子，我问我妈妈，你认为你能在一周内留意约瑟夫吗？
Well we're on vacation.
嗯，我们在度假。
Could you keep an eye on him.
能不能一直盯着他看。
Well that means could you could you let him come over and live with you and take care of him.
那么这意味着你能不能让他过来和你住在一起照顾他。
But keep an eye on means to care about that thing or pay attention to it.
但要留意关心那件事或关注它的方式。
We could also use it for for example a price.
例如，我们也可以将其用作价格。
You know prices go up and down for things and maybe we want to buy something but we're waiting for that
你知道东西的价格会涨跌，也许我们想买东西，但我们正在等待
thing to be cheap enough.
东西要够便宜。
The price is too high right now waiting for it to go down.
现在价格太高了，等它下来。
I'm keeping an eye on the price of the latest iPhone when it gets low enough.
当它变得足够低时，我会密切关注最新款 iPhone 的价格。
I'm going to buy it.
我要去买它。
I'll buy it.
我会买。
I'm going to get it I'm going to get it.
我会得到它我会得到它。
And keeping an eye on the price.
并密切关注价格。
The prices are not at not exactly a real thing is it goes up and down.
价格并不完全是真实的，它会上下波动。
So that's the thing I'm paying attention to.
所以这就是我正在关注的事情。
OK.
好的。
There's a really useful expression and it can be used in all kinds of different situations for physical
有一个非常有用的表达方式，它可以用于各种不同的身体状况
things and non physical things non-physical things.
事物和非物质事物 非物质事物。
I'm keeping my eye on you.
我一直盯着你。
That one's a little critical.
那个有点挑剔。
That means I may be expected to do something bad.
这意味着我可能会做坏事。
That's OK too.
那也没关系。
You can use it in that situation as well.
您也可以在这种情况下使用它。